{
    "subject": "resource/St._Catharines",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/Canada",
    "human_readable": "St. Catharines is located in Canada.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8980206251144409,
            "question": "Where is St. Catharines located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8589960932731628,
            "question": "What province or territory is St. Catharines in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6858844757080078,
            "question": "Where would you find St. Catharines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.683907687664032,
            "question": "What country is St. Catharines in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5131967067718506,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks in St. Catharines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5020473599433899,
            "question": "Is St. Catharines a major city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3045147657394409,
            "question": "Is St. Catharines in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13505975902080536,
            "question": "What are some well-known cities in Canada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13141043484210968,
            "question": "Can you name a city in Canada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13059969246387482,
            "question": "Could you tell me about some Canadian cities?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=St. Catharines is located in Canada.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5785_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a city in Canada?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5785_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some well-known cities in Canada?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5785_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is St. Catharines in the United States?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5785_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5785_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5785_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5785_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5785_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5785_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5785_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5785_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5785_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5785_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5785_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple pieces of information that confirm St. Catharines is indeed located in Canada, supporting the statement \"St. Catharines is located in Canada.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}